Jun Wang | Resume 2021

Xuanhua Road No. 299, Huayang Street, Changning, Shanghai 200050 Shanghai - China

□ +86 13795239883 • ☑ yarco@139.com • ⑤ www.bbish.net

About Me

Hi, My name is Yarco Wong (Jun Wong in Chinese). I'm a web application developer with over 7 years experiences. I've done many projects and I have my own thinkings in programming.

My interests in programmings are huge wide, I can work with other buddies who know other programming languages, including "Python, Nodejs" even "Golang, rust".

I also have interesting in Data analysis, Data visualization and AI/DL. And I've done several projects

I believe lifelong learning, the above technologies are all learnt by myself.

Education

Zhejiang Institution of Engineering and Technology

Hangzhou

Computer Science, Undergraduate

1999-2002

c/c++ programming language, data structure, and during school time, I learned HTML/web development myself.

Experience

Vocational...

Ningbo

Rixing Manufactory Software Developer

2020-2021

My main target is enterprises informatization:

- 1. Maintenance/Developing ERP/T100 FourJs / Genero BDL (c like programming language), and also fix bugs and add features;
- 2. Data visualization using FineReport SQL, dashboard(Js scroll bar) to display current status of the manufactory:
- 3. E-cology OA create several workflows for human resource management, ex. Leave Application;
- 4. PLM arrange meetings for 3rd party vendors, and manage the process.

keywords: ERP, OA, PLM, SQLs, Javascript, BDL

NEWBAND Shanghai

Sr. Developer 2016-2017

- 1. Backends for Music courses app developing REST API backend based on Symfony framework
- 2. Project management: code review, testing and documentation keywords: PHP, Symfony, CI, TDD/BDD, docker, REST, Redis

LOGIC SOLUTIONS, INC. CHINA

2014-2015 Leader

1. Maintenance old projects in python/nodejs/php

2. Estimation the time for adding new features

3. Review code

keywords: NodeJs, Python, Django, PHP, Javascript

FORBES CHINA Shanghai 2014-2014 Leader

Maintenance company's own website, Hot spot analyse, CDN etc.

WIREDCRAFT Shanghai 2011-2012

Developer

1. Add new feature to Drupal project

2. Developing chat system using NodeJs (with Github REST)

keywords: Drupal, NodeJs, ExpressJs, Markdown

SISTOWN Shanghai Leader 2009–2010

1. Developing SNS website

2. Using Drupal 6.0 to develop a website related to New Zealand stock marketing.

keywords: Drupal, PHP, Javascript

MEZI MEDIA, CHINA Shanghai 2006-2008 Developer

1. Migrate SEM scripts from Perl/Java to PHP

2. SEM daily monitor, SOAP client to fetch data from Google/Yahoo

keywords: Java, Perl, PHP, SOAP, MySQL

GANSHAN AD, SHANGHAI Shanghai

2005-2006 Developer

1. Maintenance company's website 2. Flash games (actionscript)

keywords: Flash, Actionscript, PHP, Javascript

LINUX PLUS, NINGBO Ningbo

Developer 1. Maintenance company's website

2. Test system in PHP

keywords: PHP, Linux, Javascript

Languages

Chinese: Native Language

English: Workable

Spanish, German: Entry Level

Computer skills

PHP: Laravel, Symfony, Raw Javascript: VueJs, ReactJs, Chrome Extension

Python: PyTorch NodeJs: ExpressJs 2003-2004

Shanghai